[{"answer": " Hi, Ms. Miles.  Thanks for meeting with me today", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 16, "question": "", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Sure.  Its my pleasure.  And please, call me Cindy", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Hi, Ms. Miles.  Thanks for meeting with me today", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " OK.  Well, I wanted to talk to you today because Im writing an article abou", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Sure.  Its my pleasure.  And please, call me Cindy", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Of course.  What would you like to know", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 22, "question": " OK.  Well, I wanted to talk to you today because Im writing an article abou", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Basically the system from when kids start school until college", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Of course.  What would you like to know", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " All right.  Kids in the U.S. start going to school when theyre about five or six", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Basically the system from when kids start school until college", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " So, they must start school at age five or six", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 28, "question": " All right.  Kids in the U.S. start going to school when theyre about five or six", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " Thats right.  And first they go to primary, or elementary, school for five to si", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 32, "question": " So, they must start school at age five or six", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " Does primary school and elementary school mean the same thing", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Thats right.  And first they go to primary, or elementary, school for five to si", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Yes.  Then, after that they go to secondary school.  Usually, its to middle schoo", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Does primary school and elementary school mean the same thing", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " So, how long do they go to school in total", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Yes.  Then, after that they go to secondary school.  Usually, its to middle schoo", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " If a student finishes elementary, middle, and high school, its 12 years.  We sa", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 42, "question": " So, how long do they go to school in total", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " OK.  I see", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 46, "question": " If a student finishes elementary, middle, and high school, its 12 years.  We sa", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " After high school graduation, students then have the option to continue on fo", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 47, "question": " OK.  I see", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " What does that mean", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 51, "question": " After high school graduation, students then have the option to continue on fo", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Higher education basically means education after high school.  So, it includes ", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 52, "question": " What does that mean", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Do students have a lot of choice in where they go for their higher education", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Higher education basically means education after high school.  So, it includes ", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " They do.  There are a lot of different types of schools they can attend", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 57, "question": " Do students have a lot of choice in where they go for their higher education", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Oh, that should be interesting for my readers.  Can you tell me about them", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 58, "question": " They do.  There are a lot of different types of schools they can attend", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Sure.  Lets see There are state colleges and universities and privat", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Oh, that should be interesting for my readers.  Can you tell me about them", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Um-hmmm", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Sure.  Lets see There are state colleges and universities and privat", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " There are also community colleges", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Um-hmmm", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Whats the difference with those", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 66, "question": " There are also community colleges", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Theyre two-year public colleges.  They offer classes for students, as well as fo", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 67, "question": " Whats the difference with those", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Do they offer degrees", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Theyre two-year public colleges.  They offer classes for students, as well as fo", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " They do.  Associates degrees", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Do they offer degrees", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Are they as good as a Bachelors degree", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 76, "question": " They do.  Associates degrees", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " It just depends on what kind of job the student wants to have.  For certain jobs", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Are they as good as a Bachelors degree", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Do a lot of international students get Associates degrees", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 82, "question": " It just depends on what kind of job the student wants to have.  For certain jobs", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " You know, I think most get four-year degrees", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 83, "question": " Do a lot of international students get Associates degrees", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Is there any other important information you think I should include in m", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 84, "question": " You know, I think most get four-year degrees", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " I dont think so.  Thats the basic outline of the U.S. education system.  If yo", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 88, "question": " Is there any other important information you think I should include in m", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " I will.  Thanks for your time", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 92, "question": " I dont think so.  Thats the basic outline of the U.S. education system.  If yo", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": "Youre welcome", "docId": "06-10", "aSentId": 93, "question": " I will.  Thanks for your time", "qSentId": 92}]
